Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - E-H
        - Friction Groove - The black box, 1985; SR-24872; Friction Groove (Box 33)
          Catalog # 81262-1; A-side Matrix # ST A 855693C 1-1
        - Friends Of Distinction - Grazin', 1969; SR-24873; Friends Of Distinction (Box 33)
          Catalog # SF 8032; A-side Matrix # WPRS 8347-1
        - Friendship - Tighten up, 1979; SR-24874; Friendship (Box 33)
          Catalog # AS-11437; A-side Matrix # ASS-11437A
        - Frisky - Frisky, 1979; SR-24875; Frisky (Box 33)
          Catalog # VSD 79430; A-side Matrix # V SD79430A-1B
          Vanguard
        - Front 242 - Official version, 1987; SR-24876; Front 242 (Box 33)
          Catalog # WAX 026; A-side Matrix # WAX-026-A RRE LP 5-A1
          Wax Trax! Record
        - Front Line Orchestra - Don't turn your back on me, 1982; SR-24877; Front Line Orchestra (Box 33)
          Catalog # QRFC 012; A-side Matrix # QRFC-012-A
        - Fuego - Misa Criolia (we are the children), 1981; SR-24878; Fuego (Box 33)
          Catalog # 7902; A-side Matrix # 7902-A Z3
          Montage Records
        - Fugi - Mary, don't take me on no bad trip, 1997; SR-24879; Fugi (Box 33)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0009; A-side Matrix # DEL-PP 0009-A
        - Full Force - Full Force, 1985; SR-24880; Full Force (Box 33)
          Catalog # BFC 40117; A-side Matrix # AL-40117-1C
          CBS
        - Full Force - Turn you on, 1980; SR-24881; Full Force (Box 33)
          Catalog # DA 1003 A; A-side Matrix # DA-1003-A
          Dazz Records
        - Full Force - Unfaithful so much, 1986; SR-24882; Full Force (Box 33)
          Catalog # 44-05955; A-side Matrix # XSS-175413-1A
        - Fun-Da-Mental - Mother India, 1995; SR-24883; Fun-Da-Mental (Box 33)
          Catalog # NAT 55T; A-side Matrix # NAT 55TA2
          Nation Records
        - Fun-Da-Mental - Ja Sha-taan, 1997; SR-25083; Fun-Da-Mental; Khan, Nawazish Ali (Box 33)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # FUN PROMO 1 A
        - Funk Club - Funky and then some, 1989; SR-24884; Funk Club (Box 33)
          Catalog # Z 45170; A-side Matrix # PAL-45170-1A
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - Funk, Johnny - In the ghetto; Here comes Johnny, 1996; SR-24885; Funk, Johnny (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24886. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 303-04; A-side Matrix # 303-04A
          303 Records
        - Funk, Johnny - In the ghetto; Here comes Johnny, 1996; SR-24886; Funk, Johnny (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24885. 2 copies.
        - Funkadelic - Finest, 1997; SR-24887; Funkadelic (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24888. Double album.
          Catalog # SEWZ 115; A-side Matrix # SEWD-115-A1
        - Funkadelic - Maggot brained, 1997; SR-24888; Funkadelic (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24887. Double album.
          Catalog # SEWZ 115; A-side Matrix # SEWZ-115-A1
        - Funkadelic - Connections & disconnections, 1981; SR-24889; Funkadelic (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24890. 2 copies.
          Catalog # JW-37087; A-side Matrix # JW-37087-AS-1B
          LAX Records
        - Funkadelic - Connections & disconnections, 1981; SR-24890; Funkadelic (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24889. 2 copies.
        - Funkadelic - The electric spanking of War Babies, 1981; SR-24891; Funkadelic (Box 33)
          Catalog # BSK 3482; A-side Matrix # B-15827-S2 BSK-1-3482 52
        - Funkapolitan - Run run run, 1982; SR-24892; Funkapolitan (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24893. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 4Z9 02763; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-02763-3-AG
          Pavillion
        - Funkapolitan - Run run run, 1982; SR-24893; Funkapolitan (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24892. 2 copies.
        - Funki Porcini - King Ashabanapal, 1995; SR-24894; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          Catalog # ZEN 1237; A-side Matrix # ZEN 1237 A2
          Ninja Tune
        - Funki Porcini - Love, pussycats & carwrecks (disc one), 1996; SR-24895; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24896. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 23; A-side Matrix # ZEN 23 A1
        - Funki Porcini - Love, pussycats & carwrecks (disc two), 1996; SR-24896; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24895. Double album.
          Catalog # ZEN 23; A-side Matrix # ZEN 23 C1
        - Funki Porcini - Hed phone sex (disc one), 1995; SR-24897; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24898; SR-24899. Triple album.
          Catalog # ZEN 17; A-side Matrix # ZEN-17 A1
        - Funki Porcini - Hed phone sex (disc two), 1995; SR-24898; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24897; SR-24899. Triple album.
          Catalog # ZEN 17; A-side Matrix # ZEN-17-C1
        - Funki Porcini - Hed phone sex (disc three), 1995; SR-24899; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          In same jacket as # SR-24897; SR-24898. Triple album.
          Catalog # ZEN 17; A-side Matrix # ZEN-17-E1
        - Funki Porcini - Dubble, 1995; SR-24900; Funki Porcini (Box 33)
          Catalog # ZEN 1231; A-side Matrix # ZEN-1231 A1
        - Funkmaster Flex - The tunnel (disc two), 1999; SR-24901; Funkmaster Flex; Big Kap (Box 33)
          Catalog # 314 538 258-1; A-side Matrix # 314-546-811-1A
          Def Jam 2000
        - Funky Poets - True to life, 1993; SR-24902; Funky Poets (Box 34)
          Catalog # 474211 1; A-side Matrix # 01-474211-20-1A 1
          550 Music
        - Funtopia - Freedom, 1989; SR-24903; Funtopia; Polo, Jimmi (Box 34)
          Catalog # GEET 14R; A-side Matrix # GEE-T-14-R-A1
          Gee Street
        - Futures - Past, present and the Futures, 1978; SR-24904; Futures (Box 34)
          Catalog # JZ 35458; A-side Matrix # PIR AL-35458-1A
        - Funky Drummer Camille - Volume I, 1994; SR-24905; Funky Drummer Camille; G-Clef (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24906. Different discs.
          Catalog # TUF LP 0619; A-side Matrix # TUF-LP-0619-A
          Tuff City
        - Funky Drummer Camille - Volume II, 1994; SR-24906; Funky Drummer Camille; G-Clef (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24905. Different discs. No Discogs entry.
          Catalog # TUF LP 0620; A-side Matrix # TUF-LP-0620-A
        - G:Netic - Plasticity; Dub (recorded in Dubly), 1996; SR-24907; G:Netic (Box 34)
          Catalog # SM-9046-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9046-0-A
          Sm:)e Communications
        - Galaxxy - We like to party, 1982; SR-24908; Galaxxy; Aikens, Ron (Box 34)
          Catalog # P-8785; A-side Matrix # P-8785-C
          Pop Art Records
        - Gang Of Four - I love a man in a uniform, 1982; SR-24909; Gang Of Four; Gang Of 4 (Box 34)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1050; A-side Matrix # B-16914-52-RE1 PRO-A1-1050 S-2-RE1
        - Gang Of 4 - Hard, 1983; SR-24910; Gang Of Four; Gang Of 4 (Box 34)
          Catalog # 1-23936; A-side Matrix # 1-23936-A RE-1-SH-1 B-18416-RE1
        - Gap Band - Gap Band VI, 1984; SR-24911; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # TEL8-5708; A-side Matrix # TEL8-5708-AS-RE1-1
          Total Experience Records
        - Gap Band - The 12" collection, 1986; SR-24912; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # 422-826 808-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422-826-808-1-AS-ES
        - Gap Band - Gap Band VII, 1985; SR-24913; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # TEL8-5714; A-side Matrix # TEL8-5714-AS RE1-1
        - Gap Band - The Gap Band, 1979; SR-24914; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # SRM-1-3758; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3758-A2-1-1
        - Gap Band - Gap Band III, 1980; SR-24915; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # SRM-1-4003; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-4003-AS RE
        - Gap Band - Strike a groove, 1983; SR-24916; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # PB 6026; A-side Matrix # PB-6026-A
          Passport Records
        - Gap Band - I don't believe you want to get up and dance (oops, up side your head), 1979; SR-24917; Gap Band (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24918. 2 copies. Promo
          Catalog # MK-127; A-side Matrix # MK-127-A1-1
        - Gap Band - I don't believe you want to get up and dance (oops, up side your head), 1979; SR-24918; Gap Band (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24917. 2 copies. Promo
        - Gap Band - The Gap Band, 1977; SR-24919; Gap Band (Box 34)
          Catalog # BJL1-2168; A-side Matrix # BJL1-2168A-155
          Tattoo Records
        - Garbage - Garbage (disc one), 1995; SR-24920; Garbage (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24921. Double album.
          Catalog # L 31450; A-side Matrix # L 31450-1 A1
          Mushroom
        - Garbage - Garbage (disc two), 1995; SR-24921; Garbage (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24920. Double album.
          Catalog # L 31450; A-side Matrix # L 31450-2 A1
        - Gage, Yvonne - Garden of Eve, 1981; SR-24922; Gage, Yvonne (Box 34)
          Catalog # DMD 294; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40408-2
        - Gardner, June - 99 plus one, 1999; SR-24923; Gardner, June (Box 34)
          Catalog # NTI LP 7103; A-side Matrix # NT1 LP 7103 A
          Night Train International
        - Gardner, Taana - Heartbeat, 1981; SR-24924; Gardner, Taana; Levan, Larry (Box 34)
          Catalog # WES-22132; A-side Matrix # WES-22132-70450-1A
          West End Records
        - Gardner, Taana - Work that body, 2000; SR-24925; Gardner, Taana (Box 34)
          Catalog # WES-1002; A-side Matrix # WES-1002-80001
        - Gardner, Taana - Heartbeat, 1981; SR-24926; Gardner, Taana; Levan, Larry (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24927. 2 copies. Promo
        - Gardner, Taana - Heartbeat, 1981; SR-24927; Gardner, Taana; Levan, Larry (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24926. 2 copies.
        - Gary Toms Empire - Let's do it again, 1978; SR-24928; Gary Toms Empire (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24929. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SRM-1-3731; A-side Matrix # T1 SRM-1-3731-A-CT 1
        - Gary Toms Empire - Let's do it again, 1978; SR-24929; Gary Toms Empire (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24928. 2 copies. Test pressing
          Catalog # SRM-1-3731; A-side Matrix # T1 SRM-1-3731-A-CT 2
        - Gaye, Marvin - Sexual healing, 1982; SR-24930; Gaye, Marvin (Box 34)
          Catalog # AS 1566; A-side Matrix # XSS 169160 1F
        - Gaye, Marvin - I want you, 1976; SR-24931; Gaye, Marvin (Box 34)
          Catalog # T6-342S1; A-side Matrix # T6-342S1-2567-S-06A
          Tamla ‎
        - Gaye, Marvin - Greatest hits, 1970; SR-24932; Gaye, Marvin; Terrell, Tammi (Box 34)
          Catalog # S 302; A-side Matrix # HS-1694-2 3-17-70 Z4RS-2137-1-D
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I have a right, 1979; SR-24933; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 34)
          Catalog # PD-1-6231; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6231-AS
          Polydor
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I will survive, 1979; SR-24934; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 34)
          Catalog # PD D 512; A-side Matrix # PDD512 78NP3765 CP-1
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I will survive (the Shep Pettibone club remixes), 1990; SR-24935; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 34)
          Catalog # GIG 666 224; A-side Matrix # 666224 A
          GiG Records
          Austria
        - Gaynor, Gloria - I will survive (the classic & Vogue remixes), 1990; SR-24936; Gaynor, Gloria (Box 34)
          No Discogs entry
          Catalog # 9031-72651-0; A-side Matrix # 903 172651-0-A
        - Gearwhore - Drive (disc one), 1998; SR-24937; Gearwhore (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24938. Double album.
          Catalog # ASW6240; A-side Matrix # S-38572 ASW 6240
          Astralwerks
        - Gearwhore - Drive (disc two), 1998; SR-24938; Gearwhore (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24937. Double album.
          Catalog # ASW6240; A-side Matrix # S-38574 ASW 6240
        - Geeneus - Anywhere, 2001; SR-24939; Geeneus; GodsGift; Plague; Major Ace (Box 34)
          Catalog # PAY 001; A-side Matrix # PAY 001-B --JTS--
          Pay As U Go Recordings
        - Gemini Brass - Keep on the right side, 1978; SR-24940; Gemini Brass (Box 34)
          Catalog # GR-002; A-side Matrix # GR-002-A
          Gemini Records
          Canada
        - General Kane - Wide open, 1987; SR-24941; General Kane (Box 34)
          Catalog # 6238ML; A-side Matrix # 6238ML-A 15A YZL
        - General Kane - In full chill, 1986; SR-24942; General Kane (Box 34)
          Catalog # ZL72538; A-side Matrix # DM B-6337 A-1-10-86
        - Genesis - Genesis, 1983; SR-24943; Genesis (Box 34)
          Catalog # 80116-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-835303-A
        - Georgio - Georgio, 1988; SR-24944; Georgio (Box 34)
          Catalog # MOT-6263; A-side Matrix # MOT 8457 HV-3
        - Georgio - Sexappeal, 1987; SR-24945; Georgio (Box 34)
          Catalog # 6229ML; A-side Matrix # 6229ML-A-15B
        - Gerrard, Donny - Donny Gerrard, 1976; SR-24946; Gerrard, Donny (Box 34)
          Catalog # G-1002; A-side Matrix # G1002-1A
          Greedy Records Ltd.
        - Geto Boys - We can't be stopped, 1991; SR-24947; Geto Boys (Box 34)
          Catalog # SL 57161; A-side Matrix # SL-A-57161-Z2
          Priority Records
        - Geto Boys - The Geto Boys, 1990; SR-24948; Geto Boys (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24949. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DEF 24306; A-side Matrix # DEF 24306-A SR 1-DMM SP 1-1
          Def American Recordings
        - Geto Boys - The Geto Boys, 1990; SR-24949; Geto Boys (Box 34)
          In same jacket as # SR-24948. 2 copies.
        - Gettovetts - Missionaries moving, 1988; SR-24950; Gettovetts (Box 34)
          Catalog # 90916-1; A-side Matrix # ST IL 886877-A
        - Geyer, Reneé - So lucky, 1981; SR-24951; Geyer, Reneé (Box 34)
          Catalog # L-37554; A-side Matrix # SMX57289
          Australia
        - Renee Geyer Band - Really really love you, 1976; SR-24952; Renee Geyer Band; Geyer, Reneé (Box 34)
          Catalog # VPL1-0120-G; A-side Matrix # VPL1 0120A
        - Ghetto Electro - The Bay Area M.U.D. EP, 1997; SR-24953; Ghetto Electro (Box 34)
          Catalog # BH 85508-1; A-side Matrix # BH85508-1R1 S-36295
          Bottom Heavy
          West Hollywood, California
        - Giants - Giants, 1978; SR-24954; Giants (Box 34)
          Catalog # MCA-3188; A-side Matrix # MCA-1998 CR-1
        - Gibb, Andy - Andy Gibb's greatest hits, 1980; SR-24955; Gibb, Andy (Box 34)
          Catalog # RX-1-3091; A-side Matrix # RX-1-3091AS-PW3
          RSO
        - Gibb, Andy - Flowing rivers, 1977; SR-24956; Gibb, Andy (Box 34)
          Catalog # RS-1-3019; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3019-AS-CP
        - Gibson Brothers - Oooh, what a life...; Better do it Salsa!, 1979; SR-24957; Gibson Brothers (Box 35)
          Catalog # PRO-A-823; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-823-M1 24426
        - Gilder, Nick - Rock America, 1980; SR-24958; Gilder, Nick (Box 35)
          Catalog # NBLP 7243; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7243-K1 AS
        - Gilder, Nick - Frequency, 1979; SR-24959; Gilder, Nick (Box 35)
          Catalog # CHR 1219; A-side Matrix # CHR-1219-AS-1B
          Chrysalis
        - Gilder, Nick - City nights, 1978; SR-24960; Gilder, Nick (Box 35)
          Catalog # CHR 1202; A-side Matrix # CHR-1202-AS-1B
        - Girls - Girl talk, 1984; SR-24961; Girls (Box 35)
          Catalog # BFC 39414; A-side Matrix # PAL-39414-1A
        - Glass Family - How long, 1979; SR-24962; Glass Family (Box 35)
          Catalog # JDC 12-5; A-side Matrix # 12-5-A L-942
          JDC Records
          Marina del Rey, California
        - Glass Family - Crazy!, 1979; SR-24963; Glass Family (Box 35)
          Catalog # JDC 62188; A-side Matrix # JDC-62188-1A
        - Glass Family - Mr DJ you know how to make me dance, 1978; SR-24964; Glass Family (Box 35)
          Catalog # JDC 62177; A-side Matrix # JDC-62177-1-RE1
        - Glasswurk - The house that glass built, 1990; SR-24965; Glasswurk (Box 35)
          Catalog # MCA-10062; A-side Matrix # MCA-1003 FDS-2
        - Glenn, Billy - Raised on the streets, 1981; SR-24966; Glenn, Billy (Box 35)
          Catalog # SG5002-M; A-side Matrix # SG-5002-MA
          Sunshine Recordings
        - Glitter, Gary - C'Mon…c'mon - the Gary Glitter party album, 1987; SR-24967; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # STAR 2310; A-side Matrix # DM C-0405 A-1-11-87
          Telstar
        - Glitter, Gary - Remember me this way, 1974; SR-24968; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # BELLS 237; A-side Matrix # BELLS 237 A-1U
          Bell Records
        - Glitter, Gary - Rock n' roll party, 1983; SR-24969; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # 412.041; A-side Matrix # XSLP-1022 412.041-A
          Opus/Columbia
          Rio De Janeiro, Brazil
        - Glitter, Gary - Many happy returns - the hits (disc one), 1992; SR-24970; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # EMTV 68; A-side Matrix # EMTV 681 A-01-01-
        - Glitter, Gary - Many happy returns - the hits (disc two), 1992; SR-24971; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # EMTV 68; A-side Matrix # EMTV 682 A-01-01-
        - Glitter, Gary - Boys will be boys, 1984; SR-24972; Glitter, Gary (Box 35)
          Catalog # 206 687; A-side Matrix # 020 206687 A-1
          Europe
        - Glory - Can you guess what groove this is?, 1980; SR-24973; Glory (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24974. 2 copies.
          Catalog # POS 1202; A-side Matrix # POS-1202-A 2
          Posse Records
        - Glory - Can you guess what groove this is?, 1980; SR-24974; Glory (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24973. 2 copies. Promo
        - Godfather Of Wierd - Theme from wierd; Lazy days, 1996; SR-24975; Godfather Of Wierd (Box 35)
          Catalog # RUF 011; A-side Matrix # RUF 011 A1
          The Ruf Label
          Cheshire, United Kingdom
        - Godwin, Peter - Images of Heaven, 1982; SR-24976; Godwin, Peter (Box 35)
          Catalog # PX-1-504; A-side Matrix # PX-1-504-AS-PRC-C2-1-1
        - Goffin, Louise - Louise Goffin, 1981; SR-24977; Goffin, Louise (Box 35)
          Catalog # 6E-333; A-side Matrix # 6E-333-A1-SH-AR 564 B-15489
          Asylum Records
        - Gomez, Leroy - I got it bad, 1979; SR-24978; Gomez, Leroy (Box 35)
          Catalog # NBLP 7154 DJ; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7154-AS A2
        - Gonzalez - Move it to the music, 1979; SR-24979; Gonzalez (Box 35)
          Catalog # ST-11995; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11995-26
        - Gonzalez - Peoples party; Ain't no way to treat a lady, 1979; SR-24980; Gonzalez (Box 35)
          Catalog # 8521; A-side Matrix # S331-3X 600187-Z3
        - Good Question - Good question, 1988; SR-24981; Good Question (Box 35)
          Catalog # 1-25743; A-side Matrix # 1-25743-A SH2 B-31330-SH2 20702
          Paisley Park
        - Good Times # 1 - Won't stop rockin'; Lovely day, 1996; SR-24982; Good Times # 1 (Box 35)
          Catalog # ROWT 96006; A-side Matrix # ROWT 96006 A1
          Ruff On Wax Recordings
        - Goodridge, Claude J. - S.O.S., 1984; SR-24983; Goodridge, Claude J.; Gilles, Georges F. (Box 35)
          Catalog # GC 131; A-side Matrix # 88-5 GC-131 A
          Gigood Production
        - Godmoma - Godmoma here, 1981; SR-24984; Godmoma (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24985. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # AS-11542; A-side Matrix # AS-11542 ASP
        - Godmoma - Here, 1981; SR-24985; Godmoma (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24984. Different discs. Promo
          Catalog # 5E-552; A-side Matrix # 965 5E-552-A SH-1-SP
        - Gospelaires - I want to rest, 1978; SR-24986; Gospelaires (Box 35)
          Catalog # SL 14473; A-side Matrix # SL 14473 A-1A
          Savoy Records
          Elizabeth, New Jersey
        - Gospeller's International - Woman, 1983; SR-24987; Gospeller's International (Box 35)
          Catalog # CEL 6769; A-side Matrix # Cel 6769 A
        - Gotham - Put your money where your mouth is, 1980; SR-24988; Gotham (Box 35)
          Catalog # T-0002-AP; A-side Matrix # T-0002 AP
          Aurum Records
        - Gotham Flasher - I'm never going to leave you (New York), 1979; SR-24989; Gotham Flasher (Box 35)
          Catalog # K 5101; A-side Matrix # K-5101-A
          Keylock Records
        - Graeme Edge Band - Paradise Ballroom, 1977; SR-24990; Graeme Edge Band; Gurvitz, Adrian (Box 35)
          Catalog # PS 686; A-side Matrix # XZAL 15190-X PP
        - Graham Central Station - Ain't no 'bout-a-doubt it, 1975; SR-24991; Graham Central Station (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24992. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BS 2876; A-side Matrix # BS-2876-4118-1A
        - Graham Central Station - Ain't no 'bout-a-doubt it, 1975; SR-24992; Graham Central Station (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24991. 2 copies. Different jacket
          Catalog # BS 2876; A-side Matrix # BS-2876-4118-2
        - Graham Central Station - Star walk, 1979; SR-24993; Graham Central Station; Graham, Larry (Box 35)
          Catalog # PRO-A-818; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-818-A1 B-17154
        - Graham Central Station - Star walk, 1979; SR-24994; Graham Central Station; Graham, Larry (Box 35)
          Catalog # BSK 3322; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3322-LW1
        - Graham, Jaki - Heaven knows, 1985; SR-24995; Graham, Jaki (Box 35)
          Catalog # ST-12356; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12356
        - Graham, Larry - One in a million you, 1980; SR-24996; Graham, Larry (Box 35)
          Catalog # BSK 3447; A-side Matrix # BSK-1-3447 LW2
        - Gramacks International - Ou pa bon cauchemard, 1977; SR-24997; Gramacks International (Box 35)
          Catalog # 3A 048; A-side Matrix # 3A048AYD1
          3A Production
        - Gran Combo - Mejor que nunca (Better than ever), 1976; SR-24998; Gran Combo (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24999. Different discs.
          Catalog # EGC 013; A-side Matrix # EGC-013-A
          EGC Records
        - Gran Combo - Por el libro, 1972; SR-24999; Gran Combo (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-24998. Different discs.
          Catalog # LPS 003; A-side Matrix # EGC-003-A
        - Gran Combo - El Gran Combo de Puerto Rico y su pueblo, 1986; SR-25000; Gran Combo (Box 35)
          Catalog # RCSLP 2048; A-side Matrix # RCSP-2048-A
          Combo Records
        - Grand Tour - On such a winter's day, 1977; SR-26424; Grand Tour (Box 35)
          Catalog # FLY-006; A-side Matrix # FLY-006-A S-5754
          Butterfly Records
        - Grand Méchant Zouk - Le Grand Méchant Zouk (disc one), 1989; SR-26425; Grand Méchant Zouk (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26426. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 463423 1; A-side Matrix # 463423-1 A1
          Netherlands
        - Grand Méchant Zouk - Le Grand Méchant Zouk (disc two), 1989; SR-26426; Grand Méchant Zouk (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26425. Double album.
          Catalog # CBS 463423 1; A-side Matrix # 463423-1-2 C1-10
        - Grand Master Flash - Flash to the beat, 1982; SR-26427; Grand Master Flash; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          Catalog # SH-574; A-side Matrix # VID-222-A
        - Grandmaster Flash - Ba-dop-boom-bang, 1987; SR-26428; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26429. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 60723-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60723A-2
        - Grandmaster Flash - Ba-dop-boom-bang, 1987; SR-26429; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26428. 2 copies.
        - Grandmaster Flash - They said it couldn't be done, 1985; SR-26430; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          Catalog # 60389-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60389-A-1
        - Grandmaster Flash - The source, 1986; SR-26431; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26432. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 60476-1; A-side Matrix # STE 60476-A-2
        - Grandmaster Flash - The source, 1986; SR-26432; Grandmaster Flash (Box 35)
          In same jacket as # SR-26431. 2 copies.